Guide to the School of Art and Architecture, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of the dean of the School of Art and Architecture, 1943-1976; Accession 2002-A-099
  - Dean Charles Sawyer, 1947 - 1956
    - Subject Files Relating to New Art Gallery
      - Dedication of New Art Gallery, correspondence regarding plans, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 28)
      - Publicity, New Building, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 29)
      - Photos concerning New Building, Circa 1952 (Box 6, Folder 30)
      - Unresolved Items, New Building, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - Art Gallery: correspondence on New Building, 1950-1957 (Box 6, Folder 32-34)
    - Architecture Department
      - General, 1947-1950 (Box 7, Folder 1-3)
      - Admission application answers, 1946-1948 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Admissions, 1947-1954 (Box 7, Folder 5-7)
      - Application for Positions, 1953-1955 (Box 7, Folder 8-10)
      - Architecture Planning Committee, 1948-1952 (Box 7, Folder 11-12)
      - Alumni Day Speech, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - Alumni Dinner, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      - Association Contribution to Equipment Fund, 1952-1953 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      - Advice Letters, 1949-1955 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      - Automobile Permits, 1950-1954 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - Beaux Arts Ball, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      - Brooklyn Museum, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      - Bureau of Appointments, 1950-1954 (Box 7, Folder 20)
      - Calendars, 1947-1949 (Box 7, Folder 21)
      - Coffee Hours, 1954-1955 (Box 7, Folder 22)
      - City planning, 1947-1957 (Box 7, Folder 23-24)
      - Collaborative
        - MOMA, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 25)
        - Problem, 1948-1950 (Box 7, Folder 26)
        - Problem and plastics exhibition, 1949-1950 (Box 7, Folder 27)
      - Convocations, 1948-1949 (Box 7, Folder 28)
      - Corrrespondence
        - General, 1950-1954 (Box 7, Folder 29)
        - Chicago Trip, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 31)
        - Minnesota Trip, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 32)
      - Connecticut School Planning Conference, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 33)
      - Course of Study Committee, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 34)
      - D Miscellaneous, 1947-1950 (Box 7, Folder 35)
      - Design Department
        - Josef Albers, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 36)
        - Promotion, 1949-1950 (Box 7, Folder 37)
      - Design problems, 1947-1950 (Box 7, Folder 38)
      - E Miscellaneous, 1947-1948 (Box 7, Folder 39)
      - Episcopal Students Advisory Committee, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 40)
      - Exhibition & Lecture Committee, 1947-1950 (Box 7, Folder 41-43)
      - F Miscellaneous, 1947-1950 (Box 7, Folder 44)
      - Faculty Meetings, 1947-1950 (Box 7, Folder 45)
      - Foreign Students, 1948-1949 (Box 7, Folder 46)
      - Fulbright Program, 19*49-1950 (Box 7, Folder 47)
      - Furness, Edgar, 1947-1949 (Box 7, Folder 48)
      - Industrial design, 1947-1950 (Box 7, Folder 49)
      - Job opportunities, 1947-1950 (Box 7, Folder 50)
      - Special tests (Carroll Meeks), 1942 (Box 7, Folder 51)
      - Undergraduate majors, 1947-1948 (Box 7, Folder 52)
      - Visiting critics, 1947-1950 (Box 7, Folder 53-54)
    - Drama Department
      - General, 1942-1954 (Box 8, Folder 1-3)
      - Applications for positions, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Rockefeller Theatre Collection, Undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Student Committee report and student correspondence, 1950-1953 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - G Miscellaneous, 1947-1950 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Garvan Correspondence, 1953-1955 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Gee, Mrs. -- for discussion, 1950-1951 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Graduation, 1947-1950 (Box 8, Folder 10-12)
    - Industrial Design, 1951-1956 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Lehman, 1951-1956 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Photos (Sawyer used for lectures), Undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Physics Building, 1951-1954 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - President Seymour, 1947-1950 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Rabinowitz, Louis M., 1947-1950 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - University Council
      - Committee on Architectecture, Painting and Sculpture, 1951-1954 (Box 8, Folder 22-23)
      - Committee on Architecture and Design, 1956-1957 (Box 8, Folder 24)
      - Committee of the Art Gallery Report, 1948-1953 (Box 8, Folder 25-30)
    - Yale Interprets the News, 1948-1949 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Dean Gibson Danes Files
    General
    See also: boxes 10-17A.
    - Department of Architecture
      - General, 1955-1960 (Box 8, Folder 32-35)
      - Visiting critics, 1956-1957 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Dean Charles Sawyer (1947-1956) (Box 9)
    - Advice Letters, 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Board of Admissions, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Committee on the Division of the Arts, 1950-1954 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Fellowships, 1951-1952 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Department of University Health, 1952-1956 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence
      - D, 1954-1956 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - F, 1950-1956 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - G, 1953-1956 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - H, 1954-1957 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - I, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - K, 1952-1956 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - L, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - M, 1951-1957 (Box 9, Folder 13)
      - N, 1950-1957 (Box 9, Folder 14)
      - O, 1951-1956 (Box 9, Folder 15)
      - W, 1952-1957 (Box 9, Folder 16)
      - XYZ, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Service Bureaus, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Schweikher, Paul, correspondence, 1947-1956 (Box 9, Folder 19-20)
    - Treasurer's Office, 1950-1956 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Veteran's Office, 1950-1957 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Dean Boyd Smith (1956-1958)
    - Applications for positions, 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence
      - A, 1952-1957 (Box 9, Folder 24)
      - B, 1950-1956 (Box 9, Folder 25)
      - C, 1950-1956 (Box 9, Folder 26)
      - E, 1952-1957 (Box 9, Folder 27)
      - P, 1954-1957 (Box 9, Folder 28)
      - R, 1949-1957 (Box 9, Folder 29)
      - S, 1947-1957 (Box 9, Folder 30)
      - T, 1950-1955 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Convocation (students), 1951 September (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Exhibition & Lecture Committee (Minutes), 1950-1957 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Student Appointment Bureau, 1947-1956 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - University Library, 1949-1957 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - General Faculty
      - Applications for positions
        - 1947-57 (Box 9, Folder 36)
        - 1957-58 (Box 9, Folder 37)
        - A -K, 1958-1959 (Box 9, Folder 38)
        - M -Z, 1958-1959 (Box 9, Folder 39)
        - 1959-1960 (Box 9, Folder 40)
      - Faculty Staff Lists, 1950-1960 (Box 9, Folder 41-42)
      - Personnel Office, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Dean Gibson Danes (1958-1967)
    See also: box 8, folders 32-36.
    - Subject files, 1954-1964
      - Graphic Arts, 1956-1960 (Box 10, Folder 1-3)
      - Survey Committee on Planning, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Section on City Planning, 1957-1960 (Box 10, Folder 5-8)
      - Department of Design, 1950-1958 (Box 10, Folder 9-11)
      - Arts for Public Environment, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 12-13)
      - American Institute of Architects (AIA), 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 14)
      - American Council on Education, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 15)
      - Applications for Admissions, 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 16)
      - Architecture Department, 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 17)
      - A & B Miscellaneous, 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 18)
      - Building, new
        - Equipment requests, etc., 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 20)
        - Security, 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 21)
        - Tours, visits, facilities, 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 22)
      - Bursar Students, 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 24)
      - C Miscellaneous, 1963-1965 (Box 10, Folder 25)
      - Campus Police, 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 26)
      - Catalogue Material, 1959-1963 (Box 10, Folder 27)
      - CINVA (Centro Interamericano de Vivienda y Planeamineto), 1961-1964 (Box 10, Folder 28)
      - City Planning, Department of, 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 29)
      - Cornell University Council Committee, 1961-1963 (Box 10, Folder 30)
      - D&E Miscellaneous, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - F Miscellaneous, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Faculty, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Fellowships, scholarships, and miscellaneous financial aid, 1959-1965 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - G & H Miscellaneous, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Graphic Design Section, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - I Miscellaneous, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - India, 1962-1964 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - J Miscellaneous, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      - Job opportunities and recommendations, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 12)
      - K, L, M Miscellaneous, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 13)
      - N Miscellaneous, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - O Miscellaneous, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 15)
      - P & Q Miscellaneous, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 16)
      - Pennsylvania State University Evaluation Committee, 1962-1963 (Box 11, Folder 17)
      - Personnel Office, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 18)
      - Provost's Office, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 19)
      - R & S Miscellaneous, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 20)
      - Russian Exhibit, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 21)
      - Scandinavian Visit, 1964 August (Box 11, Folder 22)
      - Secretary's Office, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 23)
      - T Miscellaneous, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 24)
      - Treasurer's Office, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 25)
      - U, V, W Miscellaneous, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 26)
      - University Council Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 27)
      - Yale College, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 28)
      - Yale - Lincoln Project, 1956-1959 (Box 11, Folder 29)
      - X, Y, Z Miscellaneous, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - General correspondence
      - Miscellaneous, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - A, 1957-1960 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - B, 1957-1960 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - C, 1957-1960 (Box 12, Folder 4-5)
      - D, 1957-1960 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - E, 1957-1960 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - G, 1957-1960 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - H, 1957-1960 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - I, 1957-1960 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - J, 1957-1959 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - K, 1957-1960 (Box 12, Folder 12)
      - L, 1957-1960 (Box 12, Folder 13)
        Includes 2 letters from Le Corbusier.
      - M, 1957-1960 (Box 12, Folder 14)
      - N, 1957-1960 (Box 12, Folder 15)
      - O, 1957-1960 (Box 12, Folder 16)
      - P, 1957-1960 (Box 12, Folder 17)
      - Q, 1958-1959 (Box 12, Folder 18)
      - R, 1957-1959 (Box 12, Folder 19)
      - S, 1957-1960 (Box 12, Folder 20-21)
      - T, 1957-1960 (Box 12, Folder 22)
      - U, 1958-1960 (Box 12, Folder 23)
      - V, 1959-1960 (Box 12, Folder 24)
      - W, 1957-1960 (Box 12, Folder 25)
      - X, Y, Z, 1957-1960 (Box 12, Folder 26)
      - Proposed New Building Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Subject files, 1961-63
      These materials are arranged chronologically by fiscal year, and alphabetically thereunder.
      - Groundbreaking Ceremony Rudolf building (photos), 1961 December (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - A, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - American Institute of Decorators, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 3-4)
      - Architecture, Department of, 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - B, 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Bogota -Peru trip, 1960-1961 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - C, 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - City Planning, Department of, 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - CINVA, Centro Interamericano de Vivienda y Planeamiento, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Cornell University, College of Architecture Council meeting, 1961 February 22-24 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - D & E, 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - F & G, 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - Graphic Design, Section of, 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - H & I, 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 15)
      - India Trip, January, 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 16)
      - J & K, 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 17)
      - L & M, 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 18)
      - Lecture series, 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 19)
      - N, 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 20)
      - Notes -Dean Danes, Circa 1961 (Box 13, Folder 21)
      - O & P, 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 22)
      - President's Office, 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 23)
      - Provost's Office, 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 24)
      - R & S, 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 25)
      - Saarinen Memorial, 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 26)
      - T, U, V, W, 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 27)
      - University Council Committee, 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 28)
      - United States Information Agency (USIA)Traveling Exhibit, 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 29)
      - X,Y, Z, 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 30)
      - A, 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Architecture, Department of, 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - B, 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Building & Grounds Committee, 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - C, 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - City Planning, Department of, 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - D & E, 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - F, 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - G, 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - Germany Trip, 1962 June-July (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - H & I, 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - Institute on Furniture Design for Older People, 1962 November (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - J & K, 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 13)
      - L, 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 14)
      - M, N, O, 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 15)
      - National Council of the Arts in Education (NCAIE), 1961-1962 (Box 14, Folder 16)
      - New Building Correspondence -metals, mesh, mats, miscellaneous, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 17)
      - P, Q, R, 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 18)
      - Parking - Personnel, 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 19)
      - Photography Conference on Education for Photography, 1962 November (Box 14, Folder 20)
      - Provost's Office, 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 21)
      - S, 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 22)
      - T, U, V, 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 25)
      - University Council Committee, 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 26)
      - W, X, Y, Z, 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 27)
      - A, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Architecture, Dept. of
        - General, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 2)
        - Correspondence re New Chairman, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Buildings and Grounds Committee, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Building -Equipment, Requests, etc., 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Building Security, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - Building Superintendent Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Building Tours, Visits, etc., 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - B & C, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Campus Police, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - City Planning, Dept. of, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - City Planning, Latin American Program, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - Civilian Defense, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - Columbia, Missouri, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 14)
      - D & E, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 15)
      - F & G, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 16)
      - Graphic Design, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 18)
      - H, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 19)
      - Hold File, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 20)
      - I & J, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 21)
      - K & L, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 22)
      - M, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 23)
      - N & O, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 24)
      - P, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 25)
      - President's Office (mission of school statement), 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 26)
      - Provost Office, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 27)
      - R, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 28)
      - Robie House Committee, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 29)
      - S, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 30)
      - Summer Programs, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 31)
      - T, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 32)
      - U, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 33)
      - University Council Committee, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 34)
      - W, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 35)
      - X, Y, Z, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 36)
      - A, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - A&A Catalogue, 1966 April (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - American Council on Education, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Architecture, Dept. of, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - ART News issue, 1966 March (Box 16, Folder 4A)
      - Arts for Public Environment, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - B, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Brewster, Kingman, correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - Building
        - Equipment, requests and maintenance, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 8)
        - Security and space needs, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 9)
        - Tours, visits, etc., 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Building and Grounds Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - Building Superintendent (Maintenance), 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - Bursar's Office, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - C, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 14)
      - Campus Police, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 15)
      - City Planning, Dept. of, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 16)
      - City Planning, Latin American Program, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 17)
      - Coffee House, A&A, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 18)
      - Community Progress, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - Cooper Union (Alumni publication), 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 20)
      - D, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 21)
      - Downtown Landscaping Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 22)
      - Dupont (Beddow, Bell), 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 23)
      - E, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 24)
      - Education of Industrial Designers, 1963 January (Box 16, Folder 24A)
      - F, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 25)
      - G, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 26)
      - Graphic Design Program, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 27)
      - Georgia, University of, Speech, 1965 April (Box 16, Folder 28)
      - H, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 29)
      - I, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 30)
      - J, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 31)
      - Jonathan Edwards College, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 32)
      - K, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 33)
      - L (Box 16, Folder 34)
      - La Jolla brochure, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 35)
      - Latin American Symposium, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Lecture series, 1965-1966 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Letters to Danes, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Library, 1965-1966 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - M, 1965-1966 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Morse Fellowship, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - N, 1965-1966 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - National Council of Fine Arts Deans, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - Newsletters, 1965-1966 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - O, 1965-1966 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - Oregon-Washington Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - P, 1965-1966 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Peace Corps, 1965-1966 (Box 17, Folder 13)
      - President's Office, 1965-1966 (Box 17, Folder 14)
      - Provost's Office, 1965-1966 (Box 17, Folder 15)
      - R, 1965-1966 (Box 17, Folder 16)
      - Rentals Available, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 17)
      - S, 1965-1966 (Box 17A, Folder 1)
      - Secretary's Office, 1965-1966 (Box 17A, Folder 3)
      - Selective Service System (Veteran's benefits; Campbell, Hershey), 1966 (Box 17A, Folder 4)
      - Senior faculty meetings, 1965-1966 (Box 17A, Folder 5)
      - Space Requirements - undergraduate, 1965 (Box 17A, Folder 6)
      - T, 1965-1966 (Box 17A, Folder 7)
      - Treasurer's Office, 1965-1966 (Box 17A, Folder 8)
      - University Council Meetings, 1965-1966 (Box 17A, Folder 9)
      - U & V, 1965-1966 (Box 17A, Folder 10)
      - W, 1965-1966 (Box 17A, Folder 11)
      - X, Y, Z, 1965-1966 (Box 17A, Folder 12)
  - Dean Howard Weaver (1967-1970)
    - Subject Files
      - A, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - A&A Catalogue, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - A&A Centennial, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Ad Hoc Committee - evaluations, 1967-68 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Andover Alumni Council
        - General, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Annual Report
        - Dean, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 7)
        - File copies, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - Architecture, Dept. of, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 9-11)
      - Arts Council of Greater New Haven, Inc., 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - Ashley, Thomas Ludlow, correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 13)
      - Assistant to President -old correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 14)
      - Athletics, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 15)
      - B, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 16)
      - Black Workshop (Box 18, Folder 17-19)
      - Building & Grounds Committee (empty), 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 20)
      - Business Aircraft, accident, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 21)
      - C, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 22)
      - Campus Police (Box 18, Folder 23)
      - Centennial celebration, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 24)
      - City Planning, Dept. of
        - General, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 26)
        - Admission, forum, etc., 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 27)
        - Controversy, 1969 spring (Box 18, Folder 28)
      - Commencement, 1967-1969 (Box 18, Folder 29)
      - Communications, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 30)
      - Computer Graphics (not in box)
      - Connecticut College Council for the Promotion of the Arts & Humanities, 1965-1968 (Box 18, Folder 31)
      - Correspondence with Bortnick, Harvard (not in box)
      - D, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Dean's Liaison Committee Minutes, 1967-1968 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - E, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Editorial Projects for Education, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - "Elusive E in ETV", 1968 May (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - Evaluation Ad Hoc Committee (empty) (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Experiments in Art & Technology, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - External Affairs & News Media
        - Citizens Action Committee (CAC) (Box 19, Folder 8)
        - Connecticut groups, individuals, and agencies, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 9)
        - Connecticut, University of (empty), 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 10)
        - External relations, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 11)
      - Eye Magazine Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 12)
      - F, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - Faculty and staff, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 14)
      - Fire, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 15)
      - G, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 16)
      - Governing Board - Dept. of Athletics, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 17)
      - Graduate Housing Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 18)
      - Graduate Record Exam, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 19)
      - Graphic Design Program, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 20)
      - H, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 21)
      - Harvard Board of Overseers, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 22)
      - Hill Arts Cooperative, 1967-1969 (Box 19, Folder 23)
      - I, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 24)
      - ID Cards, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 25)
      - Internal A&A, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 26)
      - Internal Affairs, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 27)
      - L (Box 19, Folder 28)
      - Las Vegas Project, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 29)
      - Library, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 30)
      - Light-Sound Project, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 31-32)
      - M, 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Morse Fellowship, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - Museums & Galleries, etc., 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - N, 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - News & Views of Yale, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - News Bureau, 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Newspaper Clippings, 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - Notice to Students, 1967-19668 (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - O, 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - P, 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 10)
      - President's Office, 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 11-12)
      - Press Releases, 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 13)
      - Printing Week Speech, 1969 January (Box 20, Folder 14)
      - Provost's Office, 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - R, 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 16)
      - Rentals Available (empty), 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 17)